I'm Yorozu Baku.
I'm an agent for the Secret Defense Organization, CODE.
My mission is eradicate evil.
At least, that's what I dream about.
I'm actually a pretty normal guy.
But even in the waking world, I found...
You must infiltrate people's dreams and stop their nightmares.
Once the Nightmare has opened all of the Mind's Doors,
the Dreamer will be trapped in their bad dream forever.
How do I do that?
Find the location of the Mind's Doors and stop the Nightmare.
I'd been given a real secret agent mission!
But do they really expect me to do this?!
Protect the VIP bride.
Good luck.
I'm on it.
Do you, Koki, take Miyuki to be your wife,
in sickness and in health, to have and to hold,
to love and to cherish?
Yes. I do.
Thanks for helping with the rehearsal.
Congratulations again, you two.
Well see you for the ceremony.
Of course.
O Nightmare.
Now... lead the world into a bad dream.
Good night, Seven!
You scared me!
We meet again.
You're a priest today?
And what about you, Nem?
I'm a wedding planner!
Aren't weddings simply amazing?
They make everyone involved happy.
I just love that I get to be there for such a special day!
I'm happy to see you aga—
Seven, are you—
Seven, are you on a mission again?
Yeah.
I'm protecting the VIP bride.
Oh right...
The bride's father...
He's Asamiya, the Minister for Foreign Affairs, right?
Who could be after the daughter of such an important man?
Could it be... a Nightmare?!
Get back!
Who are you? Did one of Minister Asamiya's rival factions send you?
He's my childhood friend.
Your childhood friend?!
Not quite the assassin I was expecting...
Get out of the way.
I'm taking Miyuki out of here.
That hurts!
Not one speck of dust will touch you.
Very impressive... Father.
Are you the Dreamer?
Why do you wish for this nightma—
Already morning, huh?
Good morning, Seven!
Good morning!
How's the mission coming?
The Nightmare hasn't shown itself yet,
but I think I found the Dreamer.
The person after the bride?
Yes. It seems he's her childhood friend.
It seems?
Not someone you know, then?
He must have been infected in the bomber incident.
Infected? What do you mean?
Since we couldn't stop the Nightmare bomber from manifesting into reality the other day,
it was able to further spread the nightmare contagion.
You remember that eerie sky and sound, don't you?
It caused an explosive rise in the number of dreams in which Nightmares dwell.
You mean...
Because I didn't stop the bomber...
Do I really... have what it takes to be an agent?
I do fine when I think it's just a dream.
But when it turns real, I get so anxious...
You've already made one dream come true.
An undercover camera and a sensor alarm.
An ID with a visor.
These agent items should be useful on your missions.
They're called Zeztz Gear.
You've also got the Capsems.
Capsems?
I've never seen these ones before.
"Wing. The power to fly."
"Stream. The power to manipulate the air."
Give it to me.
The conditions are all in place.
If you just put your mind to it, you can become a real agent.
My... mind?
That explosion at the main office the other day...
It was massive, but we can't track down what caused it.
I want Paranormal Affairs to find the truth.
But you already shut down Paranormal Affairs!
True.
So I want you working in an unofficial capacity.
From now on, whenever I get information on what seems like a Black Case,
I'll quietly send it your way.
I know the Nightmares are behind all this!
If that's what you really believe...
then find evidence that proves that it's real.
Understood?
I'm dyin' here!
How can you keep this pace up?!
It's good for your health, and management is an exhausting job.
What's gotten you interesting in exercising all of a sudden?
I gotta build up my stamina, too.
For my mission and all...
Mission?
What did you get yourself into this time?!
Oh, no, not like that!
It's the mission of job hunting, you know...
That old lady needs...
Look out!
That was close!
I'm begging you, save helping people for your dreams.
You'll get seriously hurt again if you don't!
Sorry.
Right this way, ma'am.
Take it slow.
Almost there.
That guy...
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Take care, now.
Is it just me, or is the Dreamer a nice guy?
Sorry, Minami. I've gotta go.
Hey, where are you going?!
She's getting married, right?
Minister Asamiya's daughter.
Yeah.
Cheer up, man.
Eat up.
Go on.
I know it sucks, but he's the heir to the Takarada Conglomerate.
There's no way you stand a chance against him.
We don't know that Miyuki really wants to marry him.
C'mon, Ippei.
Just because you happened to grow up nearby
doesn't mean you both live in the same world.
Listen, I know "I can't forget my first love" sounds romantic and all,
but there's a fine line between being "devoted" and being a "stalker."
The Dreamer's name is Ippei.
He was childhood friends with and grew up near the bride, Miyuki Asamiya.
He seems to still be in love with her.
That may be why he's dreaming about kidnapping her.
I see.
You really can put in the work after all.
Really?!
Gathering intel on persons of interest is part of a stellar agent's job.
You've been a secret agent for years in your dreams.
That experience is carrying into reality, you see.
I can really be an agent?
Well, night's coming soon.
If his dream of abducting the bride comes true,
it will put the Dreamer in danger.
Nem, good night!
Good night!
Hey, the ceremony's starting soon.
You'd better fix that bed head!
Where are the bride and groom?
They're waiting on standby.
I guess it's go time.
You're gorgeous...!
Thank you.
You're the prettiest girl in the world, Nem, so hearing you say that is like a dream.
You're the most beautiful, Miyuki.
I've got to protect her, no matter what.
Yes. Nobody has the right to interrupt such a happy day.
In case something goes wrong...
Nem, please lead the evacuation.
Roger!
Miyuki.
The Nightmare...
Everyone, get away from the entrance!
Hurry!
Get away!
Miyuki, are you all right?
Yes...
Get out of my way.
The bride's coming with me.
Protect the VIP bride.
That's my mission.
I'm on it.
Henshin!
There's crow feathers all over this chapel, huh...
This Black Case...
It could be a sign of an incoming Nightmare.
Even if it is, what can we do about it?
We have a lead.
Yorozu Baku.
Let's make this nightmare come true!
Huh?
Miyuki!
I'm on my way!
Miyuki...
Miyuki!
Miyuki?
Miyuki...
Only the bride fell?
Yes! That's the nightmare the Dreamer fears!
Can it be... the Dreamer is the bride?
How can the bride want to be attacked?
What's going on here?
Next time on Kamen Rider Zeztz:
I never would've imagined that you're the one wishing for this nightmare...
It changed my whole life.
It's your job to find that out in her dream.
I'm the one and only, Code Number: 7.